{
"questions": [
{
"questionText": "How long is a marathon? (km)",
"answerVariants": ["38.12","32.56","42.195","48.45"],
"rightAnswerIndex": "2"
},
{
"questionText": "How many players are there on a baseball team?",
"answerVariants": ["9","10","11","12"],
"rightAnswerIndex": "0"
},
{
"questionText": "Which country won the World Cup 2018?",
"answerVariants": ["Germany","France","Netherlands","Spain"],
"rightAnswerIndex": "1"
},
{
"questionText": "How many F1 championships has Lewis Hamilton won?",
"answerVariants": ["2","4","6","8"],
"rightAnswerIndex": "2"
},
{
"questionText": "How many English clubs have won the European Cup/Champions League?",
"answerVariants": ["4","5","6","7"],
"rightAnswerIndex": "1"
},
{
"questionText": "What's the name of the MLS club part-owned by David Beckham?",
"answerVariants": ["LA Galaxy","FC Dallas","Colorado Rapids","Inter Miami"],
"rightAnswerIndex": "3"
},
{
"questionText": "What is Usain Boltâ€™s world record time for 100m? (sec)",
"answerVariants": ["9.58","9.87","10.02","10.33"],
"rightAnswerIndex": "0"
},
{
"questionText": "How many clubs has Zlatan Ibrahimovic played for?",
"answerVariants": ["25","33","37","42"],
"rightAnswerIndex": "1"
},
{
"questionText": "What score do darts games at?",
"answerVariants": ["500","501","502","503"],
"rightAnswerIndex": "1"
},
{
"questionText": "In which year did FIFA abolish the Golden Goal rule?",
"answerVariants": ["1998","2001","2004","2008"],
"rightAnswerIndex": "2"
}
]
}